Come on, we're shining, running, forever!
The sea is calling out, so ride the waves!
We're all together as one,
so let's sail in the sun!
All our dreams are never-ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
Even though our hearts have
traveled different paths.
We are best friends.
Our freedom is our only compass.
That's pointing us along the
many roads that come together.
We will keep on running forward every day.
Go east, go west.
As long as we keep looking to the horizon.
We'll see everything all crystal clear.
We're all so thrilled that we
can't wait until the dawn arrives.
So we'll just bring the
sun ourselves to know.
If the winds blow, it's waiting
where we should be going. Go.
That's right, we're
shining, running forever.
All of our dreams will
merge into one piece.
No matter where we go,
we'll be fine and free.
Cause all our treasure is our strength.
Come on, we're shining, running forever.
The sea is coming out, so ride away!
We're all together as well, so
let's just stay with us, son!
All our dreams are never-ending, so
let's wake up, wake up, wake up, wake up!
Heartbeat, we will be one! Go ahead!
My darkness will swallow the world!
Just you wait and see!
You think I'll lose to you?
I'm gonna be king of the pirates!
Roger's treasure belongs to me!
We'll ride non-stop and travel farther.
than we've ever gone And then tomorrow we
will find suspense And then commence to
Live out another day so intense.
That's right, we're shining,
Running forever. Let's go along
with curiosity. Our feelings lead.
the way straight to a brand new day Into
another adventure Come on, we're shining,
running forever Open the map inside your
heart and see No matter where we end up,
Our mods will never give up. There's a
fire in our dreams and you can never,
never, never, never stop it
We will be one, go ahead!
No one's coming to help you.
And not a single soul will be able
to leave the birdcage. Hello? Hello?
By the way, it's also useless
to call for outside help.
Not one solitary, pathetic
whimper can escape this place.
Quite the predicament.
You're going to be killed by
the people you trust the most.
Help! Somebody!
I don't want to hurt my family!
Your neighbors,
friends, and loved ones will continue
to rampage, killing anyone in their way,
even you.
Please don't do this!
I swear I don't want to hurt you!
I'm sorry!
Get back!
I can't fight it! Get away!
It's pointless to run and hide.
You'll find that there's no safe
place to be in the birdcage.
You'll only be met with terror
that'll last for days on end.
There's only two ways this can stop.
Either you all die out, or
you meet my win conditions.
Damn that Doflamingo!
You can never predict his next move!
I can't believe the factory somehow
up and disappeared like that!
How is that possible?
Who cares?
This is our chance to scram!
We can finally escape this hellhole!
Long last, I never thought
I'd live to see the game!
Praise be to the almighty Garp!
Amen to that!
Miss Robin.
Kin'emon, I'm glad you're all right.
Metal breastbands.
Indeed, this is quite the foreign culture.
Splendid.
Miss Robin, can I be a slave?
No, I mean, can I ask you something?
Uh, so like that guy's nose?
To me, it has more than a passing
resemblance to Sniper Kings.
The guy who shot down the
flag at the Tower of Law.
Yes, that's him.
His name is Usopp.
And to think he's here with Ms.
Robin, Who was moved by
the actions of a crew,
who turned against the whole world!
in order to save one of their mates!
I'm blessed by the Edie's Lobby duo!
Yeah!
Can you stop geeking out for a second?
Just shut up!
This is the same kid who broke my wrist.
I leave these Lilliputian
warriors in your care.
Though tiny in stature,
they're rich in courage.
Topnotland!
How kind of you!
We found them like this in the palace!
They're in pretty rough
shape, but they fought hard!
We're so proud of you!
Great job, guys!
Stop me! Somebody!
My body is out of control!
This is exactly like the
tragedy from a decade ago!
I know.
I know the truth.
That night King Rick attacked us.
It wasn't his fault.
He was manipulated.
Manipulated
by Doflamingo!
You're angry?
Then scream.
Suffer.
You'll all eventually become
casualties of this wicked game.
Help my boy.
The flamingo stops this lunacy!
Think it over?
Will you attempt to kill me?
Or will you spare yourselves
and join my family?
All that I'm asking you to do.
Is hold just 12 fools accountable
for rebelling against me?
If you make the wrong choice.
You'll never get to see the
end result of this game.
The stars will be worth
100 million berries each.
The following individuals
will be your ticket out.
Army commander Keros wasn't he?
The invincible gladiator.
He listed pirates too.
I saw the Straw Hat crew.
Violet was princess Viola,
but she's with the family.
And now, let's move on
to the head honchos.
I present to you the three stars.
Law and Straw Hat.
Who'd have thought we'd be hunting
the alliance that shocked the world!
The king?
He was still alive.
Poor King Rick.
He's from the Revolutionary Army.
That's their chief of staff.
Looks like you've got fans!
Seriously?
Well, that's a relief
Glad I didn't make the list.
And finally,
there's one man in
particular who aroused my
indignation and resentment
more than the others.
You can direct all complaints
to this guy as he's the
reason you're all forced
to play this ruthless game.
And the person who kills him
will get a hearty reward.
Five hundred million berries!
Oh no!
You hear that, Usalind?
Five stars, huh?
I spot a pair of one stars
and a three star, too.
What do you want us to do, Sabo?
We should make our escape.
Get to the surface.
Let's hurry.
You gotta die!
Please forgive us, God, Usopp!
Let's live in the lap of luxury!
These traders were all worshipping
me just a few minutes ago.
Save me!
Let's go!
Yes, sir!
That's one of them too, isn't it?
He's worth a hundred million!
That's the samurai!
This is quite vexing.
If I recall, this is the Scrappy.
don't you know are you there please
respond the 100 million berries
you
have
little time for
indecisiveness the longer this takes
the more people fall the more
buildings burn I don't know this
feels wrong now that we know King
Rico is innocent all this time
What if everyone in town teams?
up then we might have a shot at
taking doflamingo out it's not
just him though he's got at least
2 000 people in his family and i
bet they're more than willing to
throw their lives on the line for
him what are we supposed to do
king rico is near the
top of the most wanted
list maybe it's okay if
we take them in alive
Like, if we apprehend them,
that might be good enough.
What else can we do?
We're out of options!
Agreed. Fine. Okay.
Could have sworn that Cyborg
was down for the count.
Where did he run off to?
Buried!
Piss off, you goons!
Keep going!
Almost there!
Saru? Yeah.
Where are you?
Well, uh, I think it's
called the King's Plateau.
Anyway, I'm here with Luffy's group.
Things are getting messy, aren't they?
Oh, Robin, hey!
Did you see Mingo?
Man, he makes me so mad.
The whole thing about Usopp's
pretty hilarious, though.
Shut up, Luffy!
I saw Rebecca was on that film list, too.
I hope she's doing okay.
About Rebecca.
Yes, I'm right here. Is that you, Lucy?
Oh, great timing, then. Guess what?
The soldier's with me.
Oh, uh, hmm.
Where'd that guy go, anyway?
Heavens, no.
Don't tell me!
What are the targets?
Let's get him!
Soldier's there.
He turned back into a human, didn't he?
Tell me, Lucy. What is he like?
That's a funny question.
You mean you don't know?
That one-legged soldier, right?
He's your father.
He's also that badass statue guy.
I...
I couldn't save her.
I'm sorry.
It's my fault.
This toy soldier is brave and true.
In the rain or in the snow,
he will stay with you.
That's good, right?
He was just here, but
took off, so I lost him.
You can't start crying yet.
I won't let this soldier die.
Be strong, OK?
I feel kind of bad that I wouldn't
let you have the flame flame fruit.
I know why you wanted it.
But don't worry!
I can promise you one thing!
I'm gonna give Doflamingo
the beating of his life!
Make sure you guys all
live to see it, okay?
I'll end this stupid game in no time!
So stay safe! You hear me?
Right!
Do you even know what
you're doing, Straw Hat?
Maybe you need a reminder.
We were supposed to destroy
the factory in order
to provoke a conflict
between Kaido and Doflamingo.
Did it ever cross your mind that if
we prematurely kill that bastard,
it'll only cause Kaido to
redirect his anger at us?
Is that what you really want?
To take on a pissed-off emperor?
Things don't always work out.
We have to.
Did you even think of the kingdom?
If we chicken out now,
what'll happen to it?
Be on the lookout for those criminals
Capturing them is going to be our only
way out of this. If you spot them,
just shout And we'll back you up, okay?
Lucky: I'm here.
Now stand up.
I'm not in control!
Well, Admiral, what's the plan?
Get Doflamingo?
These people need our help.
We'll restrain the rowdy ones.
After that, we'll set our
sights on Straw Hat and Law.
You heard me. Tell our men.
Wait.
What about my handcuffs?
They'll fall off eventually.
That's not how it works!
One sec. I'll help.
You know where the key is?
Just wait. I'll look.
You know how we're getting there yet?
Yeah, straight through!
That fool, he's jumping!
I'm coming for you!
Go Flamingo!
Why are so many people
pouring out of the Coliseum?
What the hell's going on?
The whole structure shifted.
I think they're coming
from the underground.
Careful.
I bet they're the ex-toys.
Enraged soldiers.
Aggravated officials.
And rowdy pirates.
I can't really blame them if they
riot as a result of their injustices.
How did this many people go unnoticed?
Hey, Maynard.
You owe me an explanation as to
why you entered the tournament.
That was way out of line.
you're lucky to be alive
really just hear me out
I got an inside look and
learn some real dirty
details we gotta take
the flamingo into custody
I'm telling you it's for
the good of the whole
world an imposter pirate ship and
it's from the kingdom of big shots
so nations from all over the world
use this port for secret deals?
Please, don't do it! I'm sorry. Honey!
Guys, run away!
Why not, Isho?
Doflamingo is unfit to be a warlord.
We have to stop him.
We can't make that call.
We've been doing it like that too long.
The same old song and dance every time.
You've been in the navy for
quite a while, if I recall.
Vice admiral, huh?
Don't tell me you've never once
opened your ears this whole time!
You hear those screams?
That's not fear. It's rage.
No, those aren't the
cries of terrified folks.
They're furious.
That's why the world government
has no business playing God.
My decision stands.
This matter is not up for discussion,
so they're all after their smiles.
Right, yeah.
Doofy, I don't get it.
Don't we need to protect the factory?
They won't get by the doors!
They are Sea Prism Stone after all.
Besides, I have the keys right here. Huh?
The what?
You sure that's smart?
I don't owe them a drop of hope.
Treble, you're useless.
I can't believe babysitting was
that challenging for you, goon.
You're the goon.
Besides, old man, she's not really a kid.
Hey, hey, Toffee, I'm sorry about sugar.
Please don't get mad at me.
That guy had his arms and legs bound.
I didn't think he'd be able
to pull off a trick like that.
I really messed that up, huh?
I too goofed, my bad.
I didn't think I'd have to deal with the
Revolutionary Army's
second-in-command all of a sudden.
We just weren't ready.
Ha!
Quit making excuses.
It's gross.
And that's with a capital Z!
It's in the past, as far as I'm concerned.
We can't turn back time.
And blaming you wouldn't do me any good.
Yeah!
That's why you're the
number one boss, Duffy!
Behehe!
Hear that, Louji?
I'll accept your
forgiveness if you insist.
By the way, what about Fujitora?
I think when push comes to
shove, he'll be a problem.
I already had a chat with him.
I assure you the marines
will stay off our backs.
But, once we're done using
him, I need him gone.
I won't stop till I witness the complete
abolition of the Seven Warlords system.
No good will come from keeping him alive.
Although taking him out
will be a real chore.
You sure that's what you want?
Why don't you let me at them?
His voice! Oh my god!
I'll thresh them all!
By myself!
He's so true!
Why does such a huge dude
have such a squeaky voice?
It always catches me off guard no
matter how many times I hear it.
I'm going to crack up one of these times
and he's going to put me through a wall!
There's no need to rush things, Pika.
Just wait.
Patience is key.
You could consider this to
be an election of sorts.
I humbly ask the kingdom of Dressrosa,
who is more fit to be their ruler?
The Rick family or the Don Quixote family?
It's the people's right
to choose their king.
It's only fair, after all.
We only need to stomp out the
ones who directly oppose us.
We can sit back and watch
the rest devour one another.
But, Doofy, I'd rather...
I'm so sorry, Master Pika. Forgive him.
He's new around here.
He wasn't prepared to hear you.
Sorry, sorry.
Buried forever.
You'll be entombed in a sea of stones!
Wait, Lurtpika!
Gatling girl!
If you're gonna kill him, you can at
least leave a body for his family.
I mean, we're not evil, right?
That's a good point!
Thanks, BB-5!
I lost my mother at the tender age of
eight, and killed my father when I was ten.
The members who hold ranks as executives
are whom I consider my closest family.
I've been through thick
and thin with them.
They are all that I've got in this world.
To make just of any of them
is absolutely unforgivable.
Am I clear?
Yes, yes, sir!
All right, let's hit the next area.
Restrain anyone who's out of control.
Let's find the Straw Hat Pirates
and Trafalgar Law. Yes, sir.
That's funny.
It seems like we are
invisible to the Marines, huh?
Agreed, I hope.
They're showing respect
to the young master.
but maybe it's all a set up or maybe they're
wetting their uniforms because of the
birdcage anyway what I want to know is how
that pervert found the strength to cut and
run also where the hell is he I bet that's
got to be the smile factory crazy how
it's out in the open like
that it's practically
begging I'm looking for a laser beam.
Why is there a balloon fall in?
You must have some massive cojones
on your showing up here. Oh?
That's Big Brother Law all grown up?
It's Straw Hat Luffy!
And Trafalgar Law!
And the Pirate Hunter!
Crap!
I should've picked a better spot!
Hey, Straw Hat!
When these cuffs are off, I'll kill you
myself! Come on, Law. Not his fault.
No place is safe.
Anywhere we land, everyone's an enemy.
Now shut up! Let's run! Right!
After them!
Not that way, Zoro.
Not that way either, Straw Hat.
We found some of the fugitives.
I think it's two
three-stars and a two-star.
I tripped, some weird
swimming man baby grabbed me.
Vice, you're up.
Watch out, he'll crush you
with his super weight powers.
Let go of me!
I can't get free!
Last time I made a boo-boo.
Pistol high-heel!
No!
Yes!
My legs are free! Great.
Let's go!
Hold up.
You're worth 800 million berries.
We'll kill you. Fire!
Whatever you do, don't let them get away.
Damn, what a pain.
I wish the townsfolk would back off.
I don't feel right hurting them.
Yeah, I'll use my Haki.
Shut it down.
He who shoots often may sometimes
hit at last, but not in this case.
The Navy Admiral.
It's the gambling old guy!
I heard the five-star Usopp is somewhere
around here. Start searching! This way!
Kill him!
Why do they want me?
Look up.
Because of the terrain shift,
the Coliseum Wall is now
connected to the King's Plateau.
Let's take advantage of that.
We should find him somewhere up there.
Rebecca, run on ahead. Robin!
It's a day game!
Bartolomeo.
Hearing my name coming from Miss Robin's
celestial lips gives me such a rush.
I could die.
Now go with Mr. Sniper King.
I'll hold off the enemy. Thank you.
She thanked a worthless drop like me!
I'm so fired up, ain't
no one gonna get through!
Come on!
Just what are they attempting to do?
Ah, not again!
No, it can't be.
It can't be.
They're getting serious now.
No use even fighting
back against that guy.
Yeah, those pirates are dead.
What the hell is that?
A giant man is a huge wall.
guy, pika, lord, pika, any
fool who opposes our
family will be answering to
to me.
Now step forward and fight.
His voice is so high.
It's funny.
How does that even? It didn't work!
Say something else!
Scraat!